{"data":[{"question":"Shortly afterwards, I noticed that their work ___.","a":"was not being improved","b":"was not been improved","c":"would not be improved","d":"had not being improved","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Notice\/ see\/ watch...+ Verb (without to) :you notice \/see or watch the whole action \n- Notice\/ see\/ watch...+ Verb_ing: you notice \/see or watch part of the action","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"Good medicine ___.","a":"tastes bitter","b":"tastes bitterly","c":"is tasted bitterly","d":"is tasted bitter","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Taste + adj: taste good\/delicious\/sweet\/fresh","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"The surface of the wall ___ smooth enough.","a":"isn't feeling","b":"isn't felt","c":"hasn't felt","d":"doesn't feel","answer":"4","explain":"\n- \" Feel\" is normal verb- nagative =doesn't feel","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"I tried to persuade Jennifer not to smoke, but she ___ listen to me.","a":"had better not","b":"usedn't to","c":"wouldn't","d":"couldn't","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Would not: used to say that someone refused to do something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"Have you ever ___ in an glider?","a":"flew","b":"flying","c":"flown","d":"flowed","answer":"3","explain":"\n-Present perfect tense: Have\/has + PP\n+ Fly- flew- flown","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"One should recognize clearly where one's duty ___.","a":"lay","b":"lies","c":"laid","d":"lays","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple past tense \n- Lie - lay- lain","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"By the end of next month, Ron _________ English for a year.","a":"will learn","b":"has been learning","c":"will have been learning","d":"had learnt","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Future perfect continuous tense: We use the Future Perfect Continuous to show that something will continue up until a particular event or time in the future (by the end of next month)= will\/shall + have been Verb_ing","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"Jenny ___ eighteen next year.","a":"was living","b":"will be","c":"had been","d":"shall have been","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple future tense: express the idea of a general prediction about the future","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"Leonardo ___ in Moscow for nine years by this July.","a":"was living","b":"has lived","c":"will have lived","d":"will be living","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Future perfect tense: The Future Perfect expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future= will\/shall + have + pp","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"___ seven years since Vincent left his hometown.","a":"It is","b":"It was","c":"Those are","d":"They have been","answer":"1","explain":"- It is seven years since + clause","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"}]}